<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<DODO>
  <Categories>
    <Category>
      <Name>About Python Learning Academy</Name>
      <Id>1</Id>
      <Questions>
        <Question>
          <Id>1</Id>
          <Text>What is Python Learning Academy?</Text>
          <SubQuestions>
            <Type>CheckBox</Type>
            <SubQuestion>
              <Id>1</Id>
              <Parent>1</Parent>
              <Text>SubQuestion1</Text>
            </SubQuestion>
            <SubQuestion>
              <Id>2</Id>
              <Parent>1</Parent>
              <Text>SubQuestion2</Text>
            </SubQuestion>
          </SubQuestions>
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>1</Id>
              <Text>This academy is for learning Python from speakers who have expertise in Python. We accommodate 80% of all the requests received and they will get training from basic level to advance level.</Text>
            </Answer>
            <Answer>
              <Id>2</Id>
              <Text>Academy to provide hands on experience for Python. from 2</Text>
            </Answer>
            <Answer>
              <Id>1,2</Id>
              <Text>Academy to provide hands on experience for Python. from 1, 2</Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <Id>2</Id>
          <Text>What is the duration of Python Academy?</Text>
          <SubQuestions />
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>2</Id>
              <Text>The entire learning course is split accross multiple sesions based on skill level from beginner to advanced. So for completion of entire course it may take around two months planning each session for every 10 days</Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <Id>3</Id>
          <Text>Who will be benefited from Python Academy?</Text>
          <SubQuestions />
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>3</Id>
              <Text>Who wants to learn python and wants to automate repetitive task. This is a great oppurtunity to all who deal with abundant data and want to use automation to automate some repetitive tasks using Python</Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <Id>4</Id>
          <Text>Is Python Learning Academy for limited people?</Text>
          <SubQuestions />
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>1</Id>
              <Text>Yes it is for limited people</Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
      </Questions>
    </Category>
    <Category>
      <Name>Who are eligibile</Name>
      <Id>2</Id>
      <Questions>
        <Question>
          <Id>1</Id>
          <Text>Who can join the Python Academy? </Text>
          <SubQuestions />
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>1</Id>
              <Text>Anyone who is keen to learn python and have basic understanding if programming.</Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <Id>2</Id>
          <Text>How do I join this Python Learning Academy?</Text>
          <SubQuestions />
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>1</Id>
              <Text>A mail will be sent out to all the managers with nominations link , one can approach their managers to get them registered to this or they might be choosen by their manager</Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <Id>3</Id>
          <Text>I know C/C++/Java/some other programming language. Will Python Academy be beneficial for me?</Text>
          <SubQuestions />
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>1</Id>
              <Text>Yes, having a programming language knowledge will definitely help you , but one need not to be an expert in it to join this</Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
      </Questions>
    </Category>
    <Category>
      <Name>When and where ?</Name>
      <Id>3</Id>
      <Questions>
        <Question>
          <Id>1</Id>
          <Text>How many hours do I need to spend in Python Academy?</Text>
          <SubQuestions />
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>1</Id>
              <Text>Each session will take around 1- 2 hours and will be planned for every 10 days.</Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <Id>2</Id>
          <Text>When is this academy planned ?</Text>
          <SubQuestions />
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>2</Id>
              <Text>This academy will start by the first week of July , the details about exact date will be given soon</Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <Id>3</Id>
          <Text>Where will be these sessions held ?</Text>
          <SubQuestions />
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>1</Id>
              <Text>This academy will be conducted at every site level in India , for Hyderabad location it will be in Nalanda</Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
      </Questions>
    </Category>
    <Category>
      <Name>Pre requisites</Name>
      <Id>3</Id>
      <Questions>
        <Question>
          <Id>1</Id>
          <Text>What are the pre-requisites for joining Python Academy?</Text>
          <SubQuestions />
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>1</Id>
              <Text>One should have minimum programming knowledge and basic knowledge about automation , why it is needed . How python or any such language help in automating things</Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <Id>2</Id>
          <Text>Do i need to bring my own laptop ?</Text>
          <SubQuestions />
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>1</Id>
              <Text>If you have a laptop , it would be great. Or else we will try to provide one</Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <Id>3</Id>
          <Text>Do i need to install any softwares ?</Text>
          <SubQuestions />
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>1</Id>
              <Text>No , all the set up process will be explained in the academy itself</Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
      </Questions>
    </Category>
    <Category>
      <Name>About classroom sessions</Name>
      <Id>1</Id>
      <Questions>
        <Question>
          <Id>1</Id>
          <Text>Is this an online or classroom training ?</Text>
          <SubQuestions />
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>1</Id>
              <Text>It will be a interactive classroom training sessions </Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <Id>2</Id>
          <Text>Is it completely theoretical </Text>
          <SubQuestions/>
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>1</Id>
              <Text>This will be both theoretical and hand on session with live demos and use cases will be provided.</Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <Id>3</Id>
          <Text>Will there be any communitee where i can ask if i have any doubts related to this academy?</Text>
          <SubQuestions />
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>1</Id>
              <Text>Yes , there will be python academy communitee dedicated to provide solutions or answer your queries</Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <Id>4</Id>
          <Text>Will these sessions recorded ?</Text>
          <SubQuestions />
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>1</Id>
              <Text>Yes , they will be recorde and the link for the recording will be given after evry session</Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <Id>5</Id>
          <Text>How is it different from all the availble online courses</Text>
          <SubQuestions />
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>1</Id>
              <Text>Unlike online course it will be interactive and more focussed on explaing the real world uses cases and will be give hands on experience too</Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
      </Questions>
    </Category>
    <Category>
      <Name>Nominations</Name>
      <Id>1</Id>
      <Questions>
        <Question>
          <Id>1</Id>
          <Text>Who will nominate me</Text>
          <SubQuestions />
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>1</Id>
              <Text>You need to discuss with your manager first and then he\she will nominate you based on the slots availability</Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <Id>2</Id>
          <Text>Can i nominate myself</Text>
          <SubQuestions/>
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>1</Id>
              <Text>No, Only your manager can do that</Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <Id>3</Id>
          <Text>When nominations open</Text>
          <SubQuestions/>
          <Answers>
            <Answer>
              <Id>1</Id>
              <Text>Soon a mail will be broadcasted to everyone once everything is finalized</Text>
            </Answer>
          </Answers>
        </Question>
      </Questions>
    </Category>
  </Categories>
</DODO>
